好，我查过了
Okay, okay, I checked.
我们有伯爵茶、英式早餐茶 肉桂茶…
We have Earl Grey, English Breakfast, cinnamon stick...
洋菊茶、薄荷花草茶、黑莓茶…
...chamomile, mint medley, blackberry and, uh...
等等，还有一种… 柠檬花草茶
Oh, wait, there's one more, um... Lemon soother.
点茶的人不是你  对不对
You're not the guy that asked for the tea, are you?
好吧
Okay.
《老友记》 第一季 第19集：猴子出逃
Friends S01E19: The One Where the Monkey Gets Away
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
（中央咖啡厅）
第七床的瑞秋·葛林 你的信件
Mail call. Rachel Green, bunk seven.
谢谢
Thank you.
酷，免费咖啡试饮包
Oh, cool. A free sample of coffee.
真好，不然的话 我们要去哪里索取？
Oh, good, because where else would we get any? Ha, ha.
对哦
Oh, right.
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
- 呵，这可好了 - 那是什么
- Oh, great. - What is it?
乡村俱乐部的新闻信
Country club newsletter.
我妈为了激励我 专门送这种订婚消息来
My mother sends me the engagement notices for inspiration.
（编剧：杰佛瑞·艾斯多夫  麦克·西考维兹）
噢，天啊
Oh, my God.
噢，天啊，是巴瑞和敏蒂
Oh, my God. It's Barry and Mindy.
- 巴瑞，你差点就… - 我差点就…
- Barry, who you almost...? - Barry, who I almost...
- 敏蒂，你的伴娘… - 我的伴娘…
- Mindy, your maid of... - My maid of...
我看一下，那就是敏蒂？
Let me see. That's Mindy?
（导演：彼得邦纳兹）
哇，好漂亮
Wow, she is pretty.
她很幸运…
Lucky...
有你这样的朋友
...to have had a friend like you.
马塞尔，把饭拿过来给我 快点，把饭拿过来
Marcel, bring me the rice. Come on, bring me the rice. Come on.
好孩子，好孩子 过来，拿饭给我
Good boy. Good bye. Come here, give me the rice.
谢谢你，好孩子
Thank you. Good boy.
我看他总算了解 〝拿过来〞…
Well, I see he's mastered the difference between "bring me the"...
跟〝尿在里面〞的分别了
...and "pee in the."
〝拿过来〞和… 瑞秋
"Bring me the" and... Rach?
- 什么事  - 你好
- What? - Hi.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh.
我真傻
This is so stupid.
是我甩掉巴瑞的 不是吗
- I mean, I gave Barry up, right? - Mm.
我应该为他们高兴
I should be happy for them.
我是为他们高兴
I am. I'm happy for them.
- 真的吗  - 假的
- Really? - No.
我想，要是我身边有了别人 感觉就不一样了
Oh. Oh, I guess it would be different if I were with somebody.
什么…
Whoa, what, uh, ha, ha...
你不是说过 〝我不要再谈恋爱了
What happened to, uh, "Forget relationships.
男人烦死了〞 你的阴茎禁令呢
I'm done with men"? The whole, uh, penis embargo?
嗯，不确定
Oh, I don't know.
我想应该不能说是 完全不要男人
I guess it's not about no guys.
而是要找到对的男人 你知道吗
- It's about the right guy, you know? - Hmm.
跟巴瑞在一起，感觉很安全安逸 但是没有火花
With Barry, it was safe and it was easy, but there was no heat.
跟巴洛…
- Mm. - You know, with Paolo...
除了火花，没有别的
...that's all there was, was heat.
说真的，就是那种 活生生的、野性、感官的…
And I mean, it was just this raw, animal, sexual...
好，好，我了解
Right, right. I got it.
当时我在旁边
I was there.
你觉得有没有可能两者兼有
I mean, do you think you can ever have both?
你知道吗 他同时是你最好的朋友…
You know? Someone who's like your best friend...
但是也让你小鹿乱撞
...but then also can make your toes curl.
了解，了解
Yes, yes.
真的，我完全了解
Yes. Yes, I do. I really do.
其实，好玩的是…
Uh, in fact, it's funny.
通常你认为不会让你…
Very often, someone who you wouldn't think could...
小鹿乱撞的人…
...curl your toes...
可能就是那个…
...might just be the one who...
嗨
Hi.
被打断了，嗨
- Gets interrupted. Hi.
大家好，电影好看吗？
Hey, guys, how was the movie?
- 太棒了 - 非常好看
- Oh, so wonderful. - Oh, it was so good.
- 烂到爆 - 只有女生才会去看
- Suck fest. - Total chick flick.
很抱歉那不是那种…
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those movies...
有枪有炮…
...with, like, you know, like, guns and bombs...
或是巴士开超快的电影
...and, like, buses going really fast.
喂，我喜欢的电影 不一定要有暴力…
Hey, I don't need violence to enjoy a movie...
只要有一些裸露镜头就够了
...just so long as there's a little nudity.
- 有裸露镜头啊 - 我是说女性的裸露镜头
- There was nudity. - I meant female nudity.
好，我不想看路葛兰有前戏
All right, I don't need to see Lou Grant frolicking.
- 休，休格兰 - 休，休格兰
MONICA & CHANDLER & PHOEBE: Hugh. Hugh Grant.
好，我该走了
All right, I've got to go. Ahem.
过来，马塞尔，过来
Come on, Marcel. Come on.
我们要去洗澡 对不对  对啊 我们要洗澡哦 好不好
Yeah, we're gonna go take a bath. Yes, we are, aren't we? Yes, we are.
他们仍然只是朋友吧
They're still just friends, right?
我们明天见
And I will see you tomorrow.
没错 明天你要来 瑞秋阿姨这边 对不对
That's right. You're gonna spend tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's, aren't you?
等一下，等一下 摩妮卡阿姨有没有权利说话？
Hang on, hang on. Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
拜托啦  摩妮卡阿姨  好不好
Please, Aunt Monica, please? Ha, ha.
拜托，放轻松 明天你根本就不在
Oh, unclench. You're not even gonna be here.
（乔G披萨店）
真不敢相信我们居然在讨论这种事
CHANDLER: I can't believe we're having this discussion.
同意，我也不敢相信
I agree. I'm, like, in disbelief.
你不觉得你跟瑞秋如果能在一起 早就在一起了
Don't you think if things were gonna happen with Rachel, they would've happened?
我告诉你们 她说她想要跟…
I'm telling you, she said she's looking for a relationship...
像我这样的人谈恋爱
...with someone exactly like me.
她真的这么说
She really said that?
〝像我这样的人〞是我自己加的
Well, I added the "exactly like me" part.
但是她说她在找个好男人 好男人今晚就会出现了
But she said she's looking for someone. And someone is gonna be there tonight.
〝今晚〞 你是说真的
"Tonight" tonight?
我想这一定会很完美 就只有我们两个
Well, I think it's perfect. It's just gonna be the two of us.
她整天都在照顾我的猴子
She spent all day taking care of my monkey.
我不记得上次有女生 照顾我的猴子是什么时候的事了
I can't remember the last time I got a girl to take care of my monkey.
反正，下班后 我去买一瓶酒…
Anyway, you know, I figured after work, I'd go pick up a bottle of wine...
然后过去开始追求她
...go over there and, uh, try to woo her.
你知道你应该怎么做吗
Hey, you know what you should do?
你应该带她回19世纪末 当时还有人使用那种字眼
You should take her back to the 1890s when that phrase was last used.
如果你坚持下去…
If you keep this up...
不到周末，那个浑蛋就玩完了
...you'll be finished with this sucker by the end of the week.
那个围着羽绒围巾的是 法兰西斯医生
Now, the one in the feathered boa, that's Dr. Francis.
她以前是个男人
Now, she used to be a man.
你看，那是瑞文 我们讨厌她
Oh, look. See, now, there's Raven. We hate her.
很高兴她快死了
We're glad she's dying.
然后…怎么了 马塞尔
And then... What? Marcel.
你在玩摩妮卡阿姨的鞋子吗？ 你知道你不可以…
Are you playing with Monica's shoes? You know you're not supposed to...
哇，哇
Whoa, whoa.
马塞尔 你大便在鞋子里
Marcel, did you poo in the shoe?
马塞尔，坏猴子 噢
Oh, Marcel. Bad monkey.
天啊
Oh, God.
噢
Oh.
抱歉，巴瑞
Sorry, Barry.
- 点祝贺你订婚的小礼物
A little engagement gift.
我知道你的礼物清单上没有这个
I'm sure you didn't register for that.
谁死了  谁死了
Who died? Who died?
把他翻过来 快点，把他翻过来
Roll him over. Oh, come on, roll him over. Oh!
我们知道那不是德柯斯特 对不对，马塞尔？因为…
Well, we know it wasn't Dexter, right, Marcel? Because...
马塞尔 马塞尔 马…
Marcel? Marcel? Marc...?
- 你怎么可能把他弄丢了？ - 不知道，我也不知道
- How could you lose him? - I don't know, I don't know.
我们在看电视 然后他大便在摩妮卡的鞋子里…
We were watching TV, and then he pooped in Monica's shoe...
等等 他大便在我的鞋子里  哪一只
Wait. He pooped in my shoe? Which one?
不知道，左脚那一只
I don't know. The left one.
哪一双
Which ones?
就是那双你认为百搭的笨重黑鞋
Oh, those little clunky Amish things you think go with everything.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. GROUP: Hey.
为什么空气中充满了负面情绪
Whoa, oh. Why is the air in here so negative?
- 瑞秋把马塞尔弄丢了 - 噢，不会吧，怎么弄的
- Rachel lost Marcel. - Oh, no. How?
- 他大便在我的鞋子里  - 那一只
- He pooped in my shoe. - Which one?
就是我常穿的那双可爱黑鞋
Those cute little black ones I wear all the time.
不是，是哪一只
No, which one? Ha, ha.
右脚还是左脚？
The right or left?
因为左脚的话，代表幸运
Because the left one is lucky.
大伙儿，拜托 我该怎么办？
Come on, you guys. What am I gonna do?
好吧，好吧 你是一只猴子…
All right, all right, all right. You're a monkey...
在城市里走失了
...you're loose in the city.
你会去哪里？
Where do you go?
好，这是他第一次出门…
Okay, it's his first time out...
所以他可能会去 一些观光景点
...so he's probably gonna want to do some of the touristy things.
我去《猫》音乐剧那边找 你们去俄国茶坊找
I'll go to Cats. You go to the Russian Tea Room.
天啊！拜托你们
Oh, my God! Come on, you guys.
他马上就回来，他会杀了我
He's gonna be home any minute. He's gonna kill me.
先从这栋房子开始 你们去1楼和2楼找
Start with the building. You take the first and second floor.
菲比跟我去3楼跟4楼
Phoebe and I will take third and fourth.
哇，那我怎么办？
Whoa, whoa. What am I gonna do?
好，你留在这里等电话
Okay, you stay here and just wait by the phone.
在我的鞋子里喷清洁剂 等罗斯回来杀你
Spray Lysol in my shoe and wait for Ross to kill you.
有人要跟我交换工作吗
Does anybody want to trade?
你们想干什么
What do you want?
黑考斯先生，我们朋友的 猴子走丢了，你有没有看到
Mr. Heckles, our friend lost a monkey. Have you seen it?
我把格子松饼放在外头 是不是你们拿走的
I left a Belgian waffle out here. Did you take it?
不是
No.
你为什么要把格子松饼 放在走道里？
Why would you leave your Belgian waffle in the hall?
我还没准备好要吃
I wasn't ready for it.
猴子，你有没有看到猴子
The monkey, have you seen a monkey?
我见过主持人瑞吉斯一次
I saw Regis Philbin once.
谢谢你，黑考斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Heckles.
你们欠我一块松饼
You owe me a waffle.
好，是一只白脸的黑色僧帽猴…
Okay, he's a black capuchin monkey with a white face...
俄式沙拉酱跟腌黄瓜 另外放一边
...with Russian dressing and pickles on the side.
好的，谢谢
Okay, thanks.
- 嘿 - 嘿，今天还可以吧？
- Hi. - Hey. How did it go today?
- 噢，好极了，顺利到不行 - 好
- Oh, great. It went great. Really great. - Yeah.
- 嘿，你带酒来  - 对啊
- Hey, is that wine? - Yeah. Yeah.
要喝一些吗？
You, uh, want some?
- 噢，我很想喝 - 好的
- Oh, I would love some. - Yeah.
这样好了，这样好了 我们不要在这里喝
But you know what? You know what? Let's not drink it here.
我突然想疯一下 你要不要去纽华克
I'm feeling kind of crazy. Do you want to go to Newark?
好，好啊
Uh, okay. Yeah.
我们当然可以去那里 但在去东北部的谋杀案首都前…
We could do that. But before we head off to the murder capital of the Northeast...
我想先跟你谈一件事
...I was, uh, kind of wanted to run something by you.
你知道我们先前谈过的…
You know how we were, you know, talking before...
有关恋爱之类的话题…
...about relationships and stuff, well...
- 噢，天啊，罗斯，我不能这么做 - 好吧，迅速而痛苦
- Oh, God, Ross, I cannot do this. - Okay, quick and painful.
噢，天啊
Oh, God.
好吧，好吧，好吧
Okay, all right. All right, okay.
罗斯，请不要恨我
Ross, please don't hate me.
噢，怎么了 怎么了
Oh, what? What? What?
你知道，马塞尔吧
You know Marcel?
- 怎么  - 嗯
- Yeah? - Well, ahem.
我好像把他弄丢了
I kind of, uh... I kind of lost him.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我只是要你看着他 别让他离开这间公寓
I mean, all I asked you to do was keep him in the apartment.
我知道，我知道，对不起
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
你知道吗 我想我也有错
You know what? I guess it's partially my fault.
我不应该一开始就请你照顾猴子
I shouldn't have asked you to start off with a monkey.
应该一开始就请你看着 一支铅笔之类的
I should have started you off with, like, a pen or a pencil.
罗斯，我已经在尽力找了
Ross, I'm doing everything that I can.
大家都在找他，而且我还…
I've got everybody looking for him and I got...
- 哪一位  - 动物紧急救援小组
- Who is it? LUISA [OVER INTERCOM]: Animal Control.
- 你看，我还打电话给动物紧急救援 - 你打电话给动物紧急救援
- See, I've even got Animal Control. - You called Animal Control?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
怎么了 你不喜欢他们吗
Why? Do you not like them?
马塞尔是非法引进的外来动物
Heh. Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
我不能在城市里养
I'm not allowed to have him in the city.
他们一旦找到他 就会把他从我身边带走
If they find him, they'll take him away from me.
好吧，这样说好了 你从来没有告诉过我们这件事
Okay, well, now, see, you never ever, ever told us that.
没错，因为我没想到 你会邀请他们来这里
That's right, because I didn't expect you we're gonna invite them to the apartment.
你好，谢谢你赶过来
Hi. Thanks for coming.
是不是有人打电话 问猴子怎么处理
Somebody called about a monkey?
噢，你知道吗 那完全是个误会
Oh. Oh, you know what? That was a complete misunderstanding.
对啊，我们以为 我们看到一只猴子，结果不是
Yeah, we thought we had a monkey, but we didn't.
- 那是顶帽子 - 猫
- It turned out it was a hat. - Cat.
猫，我刚刚说什么
Cat. What did I say?
3楼跟4楼 我们都去看过了
Hi. We checked the third and fourth floor.
- 没有人看到马塞尔 - 马塞尔
- No one's seen Marcel. - Marcel?
我叔叔马塞尔
My uncle Marcel.
噢，猴子的名字就是这样来的
Oh, is that who the monkey's named after?
好吧
Okay.
你们知道私自豢养 非法引进的外来动物…
Are you aware that possession of an illegal exotic is punishable...
最高可罚到2年牢狱 动物没收
...by up to two years in prison and confiscation of the animal.
噢，天啊
PHOEBE: Oh, my God.
你们会把可怜的小动物 关在牢里2年？
You'd put that poor little creature in jail?
菲比，记不记得我们说过 说话前要先想一下？
Pheebs, you remember how we talked about saying things quietly to yourself first?
记得，不过不是随时 都有时间可以这样做
Yes, but there isn't always time.
我相信一定有更友善的方式解决 你先请坐
Look, I'm sure there's some friendly way to reconcile this. Um, have a seat.
我们还没自我介绍 我是摩妮卡·盖勒
First of all, we haven't been introduced. I'm Monica Geller.
噢，天啊，是你
Oh, my God, you are.
- 而你是瑞秋·葛林 - 对
- And you're Rachel Green. - Yeah.
露伊莎·基雅内蒂 我也是林肯高中毕业的
Luisa Gianetti. Lincoln High?
每次在教室上课时 我都坐在你们后面
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
露伊莎，噢，我的天啊
Oh! Luisa. Oh, my God.
摩妮卡，是露伊莎耶！
Monica. It's Luisa!
同间教室的露伊莎
Luisa. From homeroom.
太好了！
Yes!
- 你根本不知道我是谁，对不对  - 不知道
- You have no idea who I am, do you? RACHEL: No.
完全不知道
Not at all.
也许是因为整整4年  你正眼都没瞧过我
Well, maybe that's because you spent four years ignoring me.
说句〝早安，露伊莎〞，还是…
Would it have been so hard to say, "Morning, Luisa"...
〝好可爱的吊带裤〞 有那么难吗
...or "Nice overalls"?
噢，真对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我不怪你，你那时候很胖 问题已经够多了
It's not so much you. You were fat. You had your own problems.
但是你，真是个讨人厌的女生
But you. What a bitch.
什么？
What?
这样好了，过去就算了
You know what? Be that as it may.
看在过去的份上，猴子的事 能不能请你帮个忙
You think you could you help us out here on that monkey thing, for old times' sake?
加油，山猫队
Go, Bobcats.
我可以，但是我不帮
I could. But I won't.
猴子被我找到，就是我的了
If I find that monkey, he's mine.
哒 哒 哒
Da, da, da
很遗憾
Sorry.
马塞尔？
CHANDLER: Marcel?
JOEY: Marcel?
- 马塞尔？ - 马塞尔？
- Marcel? - Marcel?
嘿，有什么事我可以帮忙的吗？
Hi, can I help you?
我们有点紧急状况 我们在找东西
Uh, we're kind of having an emergency, and, ahem, we were looking for something.
- 找猴子 - 对，你有没有看到一只猴子？
- A monkey. - Yes, have you seen any?
没有，我没看到什么猴子
No. No, I haven't seen a monkey.
你们会不会修理暖气炉？
Do you know anything about fixing radiators?
当然，你们有没有试着 把开关往相反方向转？
Sure, sure. Did you try turning the knob back the other way?
- 当然有 - 那我们就没办法了
- Of course. - Oh. Then, no.
你尝尝这鸡尾酒 莱姆酒会不会放太多？
Taste this daiquiri. Is there too much rum in here?
等一下，希望你们快点找到猴子
Just a second. Hope you find your monkey.
噢，不，等一下等一下
Oh, no, wait. No, no, no. Wait, wait.
暖气炉我们可能不太熟悉…
Um, we may not know about radiators, per se...
但是我们对环境的冷暖…
...but we do have a certain amount of expertise...
有一定程度的认知
...in the heating and cooling milieu.
我们不是还有事情要做吗？
Uh, weren't we kind of in the middle of something here?
对，但是这些女人很热 而且需要我们帮忙
Yes, but these women are very hot and they need our help.
而且还很辣
And they're very hot.
我们不可以这样，好吗？
We can't, all right?
很遗憾
We're sorry.
你们不知道我们有多遗憾 但是我们已经答应要去找猴子
You have no idea how sorry. But we promised we'd find this monkey.
如果你们看到他，他大概这么高 叫他马塞尔他会回应
If you see him, he's about yea high and answers to the name Marcel.
如果我们能够有你们的照片 那对我们帮助很大
So if we could get some pictures of you, you'd really be helping us out.
好吧，从现在开始 你不准跟外人说话
Okay, from now on, you don't get to talk to other people.
- 马塞尔？ - 马塞尔
- Marcel? - Marcel.
（危险，高压电）
马塞尔？
PHOEBE & MONICA: Marcel?
Marcel?
- 噢，天啊 - 怎么了？
- Oh, my God. - What?
有东西拂过我的右腿
Something just brushed up against my right leg.
那是什么？
- What is it? - Oh.
噢，没什么 那是我的左腿
Oh, it's okay. It was just my left leg.
你看，菲比
MONICA: Look, Phoebe.
噢，太好了 噢，马塞尔，过来
Oh, yeah. Oh, Marcel. Come here.
- 过来，马塞尔 - 两位小姐，请让开
- Oh, come here, Marcel. - Step aside, ladies.
- 你要做什么？ - 只是一点镇静剂
- What are you gonna do? - Just a small tranquilizer.
快跑，马塞尔，快跑！ 跑啊，马塞尔！
PHOEBE: Run, Marcel, run! Run, Marcel!
- 该死 - 你还好吧？
- Damn. - Are you okay?
噢，还好，应该没事
Oh, yeah, I think so.
哦
Oh.
呵
Huh.
哇
Whoa.
噢，天啊
Oh, gosh.
- 马塞尔 - 马塞尔
ROSS & RACHEL: Marcel. Marcel.
这太荒谬了 我们整个社区都找过了
This is ridiculous. We've been all over the neighborhood.
他跑掉了，他跑掉了
He's gone. He's just gone.
- 罗斯，你怎么知道？ - 噢，拜托，现在又冷又暗
- Ross, you don't know that. - Oh, come on. It's cold, it's dark.
他根本不熟悉格林威治村
He doesn't know the Village.
现在我的脚骨断了 噢，我的…
And now I have a broken foot. Oh, my...
我的猴子不见了，再加上断脚
I have no monkey and a broken foot.
真是谢谢你
Thank you very much.
罗斯，我已经跟你 道歉过几百万次了
Ross, you know, I've said I'm sorry, like, a million times.
你要我怎么做  你要我也踢断脚吗
What do you want me to do? Huh? You want me to break my foot too?
这样吧，我也来踢断我的脚
Here, I'm gonna break my foot right now. Ow!
噢，天啊 好了，这样你高兴了没有
Oh, my God. There, are you happy now?
有，有 你踢过交通标志后…
Yeah, yeah. You know, now that you kicked the sign...
嘿，我突然不再想念马塞尔了
...hey, ha, ha, I don't miss Marcel anymore.
喂，我又不是故意的
You know, it's not like I did this on purpose.
不，不，当然不是 这只是标准的瑞秋
No, no, no. No, no. This is just vintage Rachel.
你身边的倒楣事都会自动发生
I mean, things just sort of happen around you.
你一直都活在自己的世界里 做你自己的事…
I mean, you're off in Rachel Land, doing your Rachel thing...
完全不顾别人的猴子 还是别人的感受…
...totally oblivious to people's monkeys or to people's feelings and...
- 连我都不想听 - 罗斯
- I don't even want to hear it. - Ross.
- 算了，可以吗？ - 罗斯
- Forget it, okay? - Ross.
怎么了 干嘛
What? What?
嘿，香蕉男
Hey, banana man.
噢，真是有够强的
Oh, this is so intense.
我一边的屁股完全麻掉 另一边却完全不知道
One side of my butt is totally asleep and the other side has no idea.
嘿，香蕉是你买的吗？
Hi. Did you order some bananas?
- 那又怎样？ - 猴子还我
- What about it? - Give me my monkey back.
我没有猴子
I don't have a monkey.
- 那买那么多香蕉干什么  - 需要钾
- Then what's with all the bananas? - Potassium.
马塞尔 马塞尔
Marcel? Marcel.
好 他在哪里 他在哪里  马塞尔 马塞尔
Okay, where is he? Where is he? Marcel? Marcel?
马塞尔
Marcel.
你对他做了什么
What have you done to him?
那是我的猴子，派蒂 猴子派蒂
That's my monkey. That's Patty. Patty the monkey.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
- 马塞尔，快点过来 - 派蒂过来
- Come here, Marcel. Come on. - Come here, Patty.
过来这里，马塞尔
Come here, Marcel.
派蒂，过来这里
Come here, Patty.
过来，猴子，过来这里
Here, monkey. Here, monkey. Here, monkey.
抓到了
Gotcha.
- 好，猴子还我 - 现在他是我的猴子
- Okay, give me my monkey back. - That's my monkey.
你得去跟法官解释
You're gonna have to take this up with the judge.
那不是我的猴子 不过裙子是我的
That's not my monkey. Just the dress is mine.
你方便的话，再寄回来给我
You can send it back whenever.
- 好，我要我的猴子  - 不行
- All right, I want my monkey. - No.
- 拜托你，露伊莎  - 很抱歉，毕业舞会皇后
- Oh, come on, Luisa. - Sorry, prom queen.
你在高中一定要那么讨人厌 你为什么不能当个胖子
You had to be a bitch in high school, you couldn't have been fat.
听好，高中时 我是毕业舞会皇后…
All right, look, in high school, I was the prom queen...
也是返校日皇后、班长 而你…
...and I was the homecoming queen and the class president and you...
也一直都存在
...were also there.
如果你带走这只猴子…
Look, if you take this monkey...
我会失去生命中最重要的一个人
...I will lose one of the most important people in my life.
你可以恨我 但是请不要惩罚他
You can hate me if you want, but please do not punish him.
拜托你，露伊莎 你有机会可以当更高尚的人
Come on, Luisa, you have a chance to be the bigger person here.
把握这机会
Take it.
不要
No.
好吧
All right.
那我就要打电话给你长官 告诉她…
Well, then how about I call your supervisor and I tell her...
你在我朋友的屁股上开了一枪
...that you shot my friend in the ass with a dart.
嘿，能把这件裙子脱下来 感觉不错吧
Hey, it'll be nice to get this off finally, won't it?
不然继续让你穿着 也没关系
Or we can leave it on for now. That's fine.
再加上一双漂亮的高跟鞋 整套晚宴装就齐全了
You know, with the right pair of pumps, that would be a great little outfit.
嗯…
Listen...
很抱歉先前对你的态度那么差 我只是…
I'm sorry I was so hard on you before. You know, I just...
不，罗斯，别这样说 都是我不好，几乎让你失去…
No, Ross, come on. No, no. It was my fault. I almost lost your...
不，不，多亏了你 他才能回来
No, no. Yeah, but you were the one who got him back.
你真的很了不起
You know, you were great.
嘿，我们的酒还在
Hey, we still have that bottle of wine.
你想不想来点…
Are you in the mood for, uh...
有葡萄的东西？
...something grape?
- 好啊，好主意 - 好
- Sure, that would be good. - All right, uh...
哦
Oh.
一定是邻居在吸地板
The, uh... The neighbors must be vacuuming.
只要我们在这里…
Well, ah, as long as we're here...
不是在谈那个话题…
...and not on the subject, um, ahem...
我刚在想…
I was thinking about, uh...
我们两个都在生对方的气
...how mad we got at each other before.
我在想，可能也是因为我们都…
And, um, I was thinking maybe it was partially because of how we...
- 瑞秋  - 巴瑞
- Rachel? - Barry?
我没办法，我办不到 我不能娶敏蒂
I can't. I can't do it. I can't marry Mindy.
我还爱着你
- I'm still in love with you. - Oh!
我们得开始锁门了
We have got to start locking that door.
那是我演《真善美》的时候
This is me in The Sound of Music.
- 有看到冯崔普家的孩子们吗  - 没有
- You see the von Trapp kids? - No.
那是因为我站在他们前面
That's because I'm in front of them.
对哦，我以为那是阿尔卑斯山
Yeah, I thought that was an alp.
我高中时过得不太好
Well, high school was not my favorite time.
是吗 我高中时超快乐的 你们知道吗
I don't know. I loved high school, you know?
4年都在轰趴、约会 跟女生上床…
It was just, like, four years of parties and dating and sex and...
我则是跟4百个男生 一起上寄宿学校
Yeah, well, I went to boarding school with 400 boys.
想上床，就得改变整个性向
Any sex I had would've involved a major lifestyle choice.
天啊，感觉好像是几百万年前的事了 对不对
Gosh, doesn't it seem like a million years ago?
哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh, oh.
噢，我的屁股醒来了
Oh, my butt cheek is waking up.